anybody can tell me why this picture is
on the front of your book no medicine
and goat cheese or cow so Elizabeth
since they are young cheats on tool for
100 baht if I yes and is amazing why is
high school if I hide - okay what's the
name of on the front of your book -
seven Sula take a mean sousou-sama
yeah how to make him mind it beautiful I
don't need the Tattler mainly the Cindy
okay because we are going to study how
to make your mind more beautiful email
Johanna the singing I can make then I
chose this picture now holder Senator
John tool this is your mind suggestion
either issue especially the water
assistant named you in IBM who a mystery
and the birds are small thought going to
your mind so now that just sounds on the
stinking e lenta Easter days Union home
so the mind is very beautiful now he
stirs the fish I made it okay
that's why we are here so just a waste
of a woman y'all light out early that's
what we are doing so just a woman that
sort of sitting okay now